Tonight, I want everyone in this room to know
今晚，我希望在座的诸位都能明白
赐予者
that I see you, I believe in you
我遇见你，且相信你
Hoping you take that jump
愿你勇敢一跃
But don't feel the fall
坠落无境
Hope when the water rises
愿水涨潮袭时
You built a wall
你筑起防备高墙
the survivance that we do to ourselves
我们为自己而生
Hoping the crowd screams out
愿人群声嘶力吼
It's screaming your name
高喊你的姓名
When I woke up
当我醒来
the first thing I was...
Hoping everybody in love
我要做的第一件事就是
愿你寻得挚爱
taken his hand, holding mine
让他牵住我的手
And hold sustain
永生相恋
My sister taught me what actually family is
我的姐姐教会了我什么是家庭
I hope that you fall in love
愿你真心敢爱
And it hurts so bad
即便痛彻心扉
The only way you can know
倾尽所有
It give it all you have
你才会真正明白
I take everything I'm feeling
我接受我所感知到的一切
And I hope that you don't suffer
当苦痛来袭
But take the pain
愿你免受折磨
Hope when the moment comes
愿当大限来临
You'll say
你能高呼
I, I did it all
我，爱过，恨过，活过
I owned every second that this world could give
我拥有在这世界上的每分每秒
I saw so many places the things that I did
看尽世事无常人间冷暖
What did I tell you about!
我告诉过你的！
Of every broken bone
纵然身心俱疲
I swear I lived
不枉这一生
Hello, angles
你好，天使
Hope that you spend your days
愿你人生度过的每段时光
But they all add up
都不曾虚度
And when that sun goes down
当日落之时
Hope you raise your cup, oh
愿你高高举杯
You got it
你已经明白了
I thought I was it
我便是如此
I wish that I could witness
我愿我能见证
All you drew and all your pain
你所有的喜乐和苦痛
But until my moment comes
愿当大限来临
I'll say
我能高呼
I, I did it all
我，爱过，恨过，活过
Your dream is…
你的梦想是...
I owned every second that this world could give
我拥有这个世界所给予的每分每秒
I saw so many places the things that I did
看尽世事无常人间冷暖
Of every broken bones
纵然身心俱疲
I swear I lived
不枉这一生
I'm not just 'me'
我不仅仅是“我”
I'm also a 'we'
我也是“我们”
Sometimes
有的时候
I make a mistake
我犯了错
I swear I lived
不枉这一生
I get two choices
面临两难的选择
To live with this
与此朝夕相处
I swear I lived
不枉这一生
Get up
振作起来
I, I did it all
我，爱过，恨过，活过
Or to fix it
或是解决它
Love
爱
I, I did it all
我，爱过，恨过，活过
I owned every second that this world could give
我拥有这个世界所给予的每分每秒
I saw so many places the things that I did
看尽世事无常人间冷暖
With every broken bones
纵然身心俱疲
I swear I lived
不枉这一生
不枉这一程
You are no longer just 'you'
你不再是你自己
With the loved ones together
与你所爱一起
I know that there's nothing we can't do
我明白没有什么将再是不可能的